Erin Reeves

219 St. Julien Ave• Lafayette, La 70506 • Phone: 361.877.3095 • E-Mail: ernreeves@gmail.com

Professional Profile

Erin Reeves has experience in the healthcare field for over 3 years. Her primary experience has been in implementation of allergy testing and immunotherapy clinics within primary care physicians offices. Her responsibilities include physical set up of allergy center, onsite training of allergy employee, education of physician and training of the office staff. Her experience and expertise consist of:

- EMR
- Allergy Testing
- Quality Assurance
- HIPAA

- CPR & AED Certified
- Salesforce
- Immunotherapy
- Healthcare Information Technology

Employment History

United Allergy Services, Implementation Specialist

4/1/2012 — Present

Nationwide

- Seamlessly implemented 45+ allergy service clinics within primary care physician's offices.
- Performed onsite training for clinical allergy specialist, physicians, and office staff.
- Prepared the clinical allergy specialist to self-manage their own allergy clinic.
- Developed relationships between United Allergy Services and our customers.
- Performed on site presentations weekly for United Allergy best practice protocol.
- Provided support to United Allergy training facility.

Louisiana Floater

7/25/2011 - 4/2/2012

Louisiana

- Applying the knowledge gained from different labs to better educate patients, newer employees, and myself.
- Performed insurance verification, and have also created a template to aide CAS's through the insurance verification process.
- Aided several Implementation Specialists with lab implementations.
- Trained Several Clinical Allergy Specialists that were new to the company.
- Worked in several labs that have had multiple providers, and helped develop an

allergy patient referral process.

- Member of 2012 United Allergy Services Culture Committee.

Our Lady of the Lake Regional, PT and OT Technician 1/3/2011 - 7/25/2011 Baton Rouge, LA

- Worked in both skilled nursing and acute departments assisting therapist with patient exercises, primarily with geriatric patients.
- Assisted therapist with wound care, using sterile procedures for cleaning materials used and maintaining a sterile environment.
- Aided with patient transport, which consisted of transferring patients using safe lifting techniques.

Our Lady of Lourdes Regional, PT and OT Technician 9/16/2010 — 1/1/2011 Lafayette, Louisiana

- Worked in outpatient, rehab, and acute care departments assisting therapist with patient exercises.
- Made schedules for therapists based off of orders sent from in-house physicians.
- Assisted therapist with wound care, using sterile procedures for cleaning materials used and maintaining a sterile environment.

Training and Certificates

OSHA Blood Borne Pathogen Certified Certified Clinical Lab Specialist HIPAA compliance Training

Education

Bachelor of Science in Kinesiology University of Louisiana-Lafayette Lafayette, LA December 13, 2010